声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
法语! 法国人要来了!
French! The French are coming!
我对听到法语还从没这么开心过!
I've never been so happy to hear the French!
-谁会说法语?  -她会
-Does anyone speak French?  -She does.
我现在一个人
I'm alone now.
一个人在岛上
On the island alone.
谁快来救我
Please, someone come.
其他人他们都
The others, they're...
他们都已经死了
They're dead.
它杀了他们
It killed them.
它把他们全杀了
It killed them all.
-我不能再呆下去了  -你没地方可去
-I can't stay here.  -There's nowhere to go.
必须得有人走遍这个海岸 画好岛屿地图
Someone has to walk the shore and map the island.
看看还有什么东西在这儿
See what else there is.
希望还能见到你
I hope we meet again.
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
你知道发生什么事了
You know what's happening.
我不明白为什么
But I don't understand. Why...?
你本应该对他负责 但你却抛弃了他 Claire
It was your responsibility, but you gave him away, Claire.
现在人人要受到报应
Everyone pays the price now.
Claire没...没事了
Hey, hey, hey, hey!It's Charlie! It's Charlie! It’s okay! It's okay. It’s all right.
你是在做梦
You were dreaming.
梦游罢了
You were sleepwalking. All right?
好
Okay.
Claire  发生什么事了?
Claire, what happened?
一定是个可怕的噩梦
Must have been a hell of a nightmare.
谁说过是噩梦了?
Who said it was a nightmare?
如果谁把拳头握得这么紧
When someone makes a fist so tight
指甲甚至都嵌进手掌四分之一英寸长
they dig their nails a quarter of an inch into their palms,
我说他们一定没在做着 骑马这样的好梦
they probably weren't dreaming about riding ponies.
-以前有过梦游吗?  -没我想没有
-Did you ever sleepwalk before?  -No. I don't think so.
-我怎么知道?  -会有反馈信号的
-How would I know?  -It'd get back to you.
我有个女朋友有一次 说我会讲梦话
I had a girlfriend once that, uh,told me I talked in my sleep.
-你说什么梦话了?  -不知道
-What did you say?  -Don't know.
不管说了什么 反正她不喜欢
Whatever it was, she didn't like it.
悉尼的妇产科医生怎样?
How was your OBIG YN in Sydney?
很好  她很好
Good. She was good.
你在怀孕的第三阶段坐飞机 她对你这样没意见?
She was okay with letting you fly in your third trimester?
是的  坐飞机的前一周我去做了检查 她说没事的
Yeah, I went for a checkup a week before, and she said it would be fine.
-超声波检测结果是好的?  -是的  非常健康
-Ultrasound was cool?  -Mm-hmm. Very healthy.
-感觉怎么样?  -还行
-How you been feeling?  -Okay.
只是背很痛
Back's pretty sore,
也许是睡在地上的缘故
but probably just from sleeping on the ground.
如果我站起来太快的话 会觉得头晕
I get dizzy if I stand up too fast.
还有我老想小便
And I have to pee all the time.
-吃的东西够吗?  -野猪和香蕉
-You eating enough?  -Boar and bananas.
怀孕已经有几周了?
How many weeks in are you?
你什么时候发现你怀孕了?
What was the date that you found out that you were pregnant?
-是粉色吗?  -我还不知道
-Is it pink?  -I don't know.
我是说你真尿在它上面了?
I mean, did you actually pee on it?
-是的  请给我点时间  -也许是你做的方式不对
-Just give me a second.  -Maybe you didn't do it right.
-Thomas我可以尿在一根棒上  -那是什么颜色?
-Thomas, I can pee on a stick.  -What color is it?
-多久了?  -66秒了
-How long's it been?  -Six... 66 seconds.
-糟了  -安静
-Oh, gosh.  -Shh.
好的有很明显的两条线
Okay, there's definitely two lines.
-两条粉色的线?  -粉色? 不 这看上去像红色
-Two pink lines?  -Pink? No, no, no. These are, like, red.
什么?
What?
是粉色
They're pink.
-这两条线  -是粉色的
-These two lines...  -They're pink.
好吧  首先这种测试并不一定准确
First of all, these tests are not always accurate.
不  你知道我我伯父的
No, no, no. My uncle, you know,
本来大家都以为他得了睾丸癌还记得吗?
we thought he had testicular cancer. You remember that?
-是的  他得癌了  他完蛋了  -是这样...
-He did. He's dead.  -Well, yeah...
我是说不不...这就个错误的...
I mean, no, no. It was like a wrong...
错误的诊断
It was a bad diagnosis.
听着...这东西 并不能完全确定你是否怀孕
This thing doesn't mean for sure you're pregnant.
-Thomas!  -我们应该再试一次
-Thomas!  -Get another.
我的例假已经6周没有来了 知道吗? ... 6周
I am six weeks late, okay? Six weeks.
从来没发生过这种事 我怀孕了
That never happens. I’m pregnant.
好好 听着事情会变好的
Okay. Okay, look, it’s all gonna be okay.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
Claire
你知道如果我们想要的话 我们能这么做的
You know, if we wanted to, we could do this.
不要说了
Stop it.
-不 我没在开玩笑  -我妈妈会不要我的
-No, I'm not kidding.  -My mom would disown me.
可以说已经不要你了
She basically has already.
是的 但我们用什么来养活孩子? 就靠我在炸鱼店每小时5美元的工作?
Yeah, and but with what? I mean, my $5-an-hour job at Fish 'n Fry?
但并不是只有你一个人有工作?
You're not the only one with a job, you know?
我意思是我能画画
I mean, I've got my painting.
这很好  但这不是我们想要的
That's sweet, but...This isn't what we want.
或许是
Maybe it is.
你知道吗?
You know?
这可能是....
This could be like, uh...
我不知道
I don't know.
这就像是我们之间最美好的东西
It could be, like, the best thing ever.
你真想试试?
You'd really want to try?
是的
Yeah.
Claire我爱你
Claire, I love you.
这还是第一次
Well, this is a first.
一天里你站着不动什么也不做
You standing still, middle of the day, doing nothing.
让人惊讶
Amazing.
我在做事
I'm doing something.
是吗? 做什么?
Yeah? What's that?
淹没自己
I'm sinking.
水往外流带走沙子 接着你就往下沉
Water goes out, takes the sand with it and you sink.
我还是孩子的时候和我妈妈这么玩过
I used to do it with my mom when I was a kid.
新计划
Ah. New plan.
你就打算一路下沉离开这个岛
You're gonna just sink your way right off the island.
Sayid会替你感到自豪的
Sayid would be proud.
他离开已经有一周了
He's been gone for almost a week.
我有预感他会没事的
Something tells me he'll be okay.
那你大老远跑到这儿来干什么?
So, what are you doing this far from the caves?
带水来
Bringing water down.
带鱼回去
Bringing fish back.
Claire马上就要生了
Claire's gonna have the baby soon.
"亲爱的日记"
Dear diary,
"我们还在这个该死的岛"上
still on the bloody island.
"今天我吞下了一只虫子"
Today, I swallowed a bug.
"爱你的  Claire"
Love, Claire.
这儿
Here.
如果我们不喝茶的话 怎么能把我们跟那些野人区分开来?
What separates us from these savage Yanks if we can't drink tea?
-感觉好些了?  -只是个梦罢了
-Feeling better?  -It was just a dream.
我也做过这样的梦
I have this dream.
我开着车我的牙齿开始掉落
I'm driving a bus, and my teeth start falling out.
我妈妈在后面吃着饼干
My mum is in the back, eating biscuits.
每样东西闻起来都是熏肉的味道
Everything smells of bacon.
很古怪
It's weird.
当然我没有尖叫着醒来
Of course, I don't wake up screaming.
我没事Charlie
I'm all right, Charlie.
你当然没事
Mmm. No, of course you are.
只是...
It's just...
在这个地方
...I think about you
我很挂念你
...in this place.
你过得一定很艰难
How hard it must be for you,
没有家人没有朋友
without your family and your friends.
我想我们可以做朋友 我可以做你的朋友
And I think, we could be friends. I could be your friend.
我们不必给对方剪头发 或者别的一些事情
We don't have to do each other's hair or anything.
你知道我是说真的 如果你想找个人聊聊
I just mean that, you know, if you needed someone to talk to about anything,
我就在这儿
I'm here.
Charlie
好
Okay.
-我没有那种意思...  -没关系Claire
-I didn't mean that I...  -It's cool, Claire.
没关系
It's cool.
Thomas把整个阁楼都打扫干净了
Thomas cleaned out his whole loft.
我礼拜二要正式搬进去了
I'm officially moving in on Tuesday.
-太好了!  -我知道他很棒!
-That is great!  -I know. He's awesome.
-你知道也许我们并不应该  -不行你现在不准退缩
-You know, maybe we shouldn't...  -No. You’re not backing out now.
-感觉有点傻  -他只是能够通灵而已  Claire
-It seems silly.  -He's just a psychic, Claire.
我还以为你能接受类似于占星术的这些东西
I thought you were into this, all your astrology stuff.
我知道
Yeah, I know,
但我不需要谁来告诉我 我会发生什么事
but I don't need somebody telling me
我应该怎样生活
what's gonna happen or how to live my life.
这不是你需要不需要的问题 这是个有不有趣的问题
It's not about what you need. It’s about what's fun.
所以除非你还有其它借口
So unless you have another excuse...
我要你把手伸过来
I'll need your hands for this.
那么你什么时候发现的?
So when did you find out?
-什么?  -孩子的事
-What?  -About the baby.
两天前
Um... Two days ago.
-她还没告诉她妈妈  -嘘!
-She hasn't told her mum yet...  -Shh.
什么? 我不应该告诉她?
What, should I not tell her?
什么?是什么?
What? What is it?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry. Um...
我不能 我不能...
I can't... I can't...
你要你看到什么了?
What were you gonna...? What did you see?
我不给你算命了
I'm not doing this reading.
不行  你总得说些什么
No, you were gonna say something.
你们得走了 现在就请离开
You'll have to leave. Now.
谢谢 ... 非常感谢
Thanks, thanks very much.
真是个怪人
What a freak.
救命!
Help me!
有人要伤害我!求你们!救救我!
Somebody's trying to hurt me! Please! Help me!
-有人攻击她!  -什么?
-Someone attacked her!  -What?
-他把我摁在地上!  -他往哪个方向跑了?
-He held me down!  -Which way did he go?
我不知道 我什么都看不到
I don't know. I couldn't see any...
-多久前?  -发生什么事了?
-How long ago?  -What's going on?
就刚才! 他刚刚逃跑!
Just now! He just ran away!
我们在周围的山洞分头找找
We should fan out and check the surrounding caves.
-等等等等  -Hurley快我们走
-Wait, wait, hold on.  -Hurley, come on, let's go.
我们坐下好吗?
Come on. Come on. Let’s sit down here, okay?
-你能给她弄些水吗?  -好的
-Can you get her some water?  -Sure.
Claire看着我  没事了 你现在很安全
Claire, look at me. It’s okay. You're safe now.
-你有没看清楚他?  -没有很暗  我看不见
-Did you get a look at him at all?  -It was dark. I couldn't see.
-哪儿发生的事?  -就这儿!
-Where did this happen?  -He was here!
我正在睡觉  我刚醒来的时候他正要伤害我的孩子
I mean, I was sleeping, and I woke up, and he was trying to hurt my baby!
他有针之类的东西
He had this thing, like a needle,
他用那东西扎我!
and he stabbed me with it!
他要伤害我的孩子!
He was trying to hurt my baby.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
这整个地方我们都找过了老兄
We hoofed around the entire perimeter, man.
没人看到或听到什么吗?
Nobody saw or heard anything?
什么都没有 大家都在睡觉
Uh-uh. Nada. Everyone was asleep.
我有个想法
So, I had an idea.
我在这儿找某个精神病患者 叫Scott或者叫Steve什么的对吧?
I'm out here looking for some psycho with Scott and Steve, right?
我突然意识到这Scott和Steve他妈的是谁呢?
And I'm realizing, who the hell are Scott and Steve?
我不懂你的意思
I'm not following you.
如果我是个警察  某个妇女遭到攻击了 我们会彻底细查是吧?
Look, if I was a cop, and some woman got attacked, we’d canvas, right?
去敲门找出目击证人
Knock on doors, find witnesses.
但我们现在连门都没有
But we don't even have doors.
Hurley你这么说我还是不明白 你是要...
You're not helping me understand...
我们不知道谁住在这儿  谁住在岸边
We don't know who's living here, and who's still at the beach.
我意思是大家 甚至各自都不了解
I mean, we don't even know each other.
我的名字不是Hurley而是Hugo Reyes
My name isn't Hurley. It’s Hugo Reyes.
Hurley只是个昵称  明白?
Hurley's just a nickname I have, all right?
为什么呢? 为什么我没告诉你?
Why? I'm not telling.
关键是我们得找出岛上各个人的身份
The point is, we got to find out who everyone is.
你要搞人口调查?
You want to start a census?
是的  登记一下姓名 谁长什么样  谁和谁有关系
A registry. Names, what people look like, who’s related to who.
我们要立个法 或许这样人们就不会相互攻击了
We lay down the law, people will stop attacking each other.
似乎这儿隔三差五就有有谁被捶或者谁被刺了一刀的事情
Seems like someone's punched or stabbed every other day.
我们得找出是谁攻击了她
We got to find out who did this to her.
你还好吗?
You all right?
不用担心
Don't worry.
如果你想闭上眼睛睡觉
If you want to close your eyes,
我会整晚都在这儿的
I'll be here all night.
我不会让任何人接近你
I won't let anyone get to you.
我不会离开你Claire 我保证
I won't leave you, Claire. Promise.
-我们有窗帘了  -我知道
-Wow, we have drapes now.  -I know.
我感到自己长大了
I feel all grown up.
喜欢这窗帘吗?
You like 'em?
是的  他们很漂亮
Yeah. They're good.
我不知道为什么窗帘 对我来说意味着年龄
I don't know why drapes represent age for me.
我感觉这种事情总应该让我妈来做
I guess it just feels like something my mum would do.
Sasha打来电话
Oh, um, Sasha called.
他们今晚要出去 问我们去不去
They're going out tonight. They wanted to know if we'd go.
什么?
What?
我没有把薯片吃完 还有一袋呢
I didn't eat all the chips. There’s another bag.
Claire?
我不能这么做
I can't do this.
做什么?
Do what?
你今天过得不开心?
Did you have a bad day?
这不管用
This isn't working.
拜托...你知道的
Come on, you knew that.
我知道什么?
I what?
是不是我太敏感了...
Just so I'm not overreacting here,
你要和我分手?
are you breaking up with me?
过去的三个月只是
For the past three months, it's just,
你知道总是会有些计划  有些责任
there's some plan, some responsibility,
我们得去哪儿 得和哪些人说话
somewhere we have to be, someone you have to talk to.
是啊  我只是想确保孩子出生的时候
I'm trying to make sure when the baby comes...
"孩子出生"? 是我是说那不只是...
"When the baby..." Yeah.I mean, that is just not...
如果照这种情况下去 孩子出生的时候事情又会怎样?
If it's like this now, you know, what’s it gonna be like when the baby comes?
但是是你说我们应该这么做的
But you said we should do this.
是
Yeah.
是的  但现在我说的才是真话
Yeah, well, now it's real.
你不能随便改变主意
You can't just change your mind.
你叫我怎么当个爸爸  Claire?
How in the hell am I supposed to be a dad, Claire?
我的画怎么办? 我的生活呢?
How about my painting? My life?
我知道 ...我早知道事情会变成这样
I knew... I knew this was gonna happen.
"我告诉过你这些"真是完美
I told you so. Perfect.
现在所有的什么"弃妇弃子"的头衔都套在我头上了
Now I get all your daddy abandonment crap.
你这杂种 你敢说你做的是对的?!
Hey, you bastard, don't you dare try and justify what you're doing!
我做过什么了?
I have done nothing!
-我什么都没做过  -什么?  那是我错了?
-I've done absolutely nothing.  -What, I have?
你还以为我不知道 你干的那些好事?
You don't think I've seen what you've done?
麻烦你再说一遍?
Excuse me?
你本应该吃药的
You were supposed to be on the Pill.
-你认为我是故意怀孕的?  -我才不在乎
-You think I got pregnant on purpose?  -I don't even care.
你认为这是我搞的一个计划?
Or that this was some kind of plan?
-你脑袋是不是坏掉了!  -都结束了Claire!
-You are out of your mind!  -It's over, Claire!
不  还没结束!
No, it's not over!
-我要走了  -Thomas!
-I'm out of here.  -Thomas!
John对吧?  John Locke?
John, right? John Locke?
这就是你的人口调查?
Is this about your census?
是的你知道 我觉得这是个好点子你知道
Yeah, you know, I thought it would be a good idea, you know,
记下每个人的名字和住所
get everyone's name and place of residence.
那谁来登记你呢?
And who's checking on you?
呃...我自己
Uh, me.
开玩笑了
It was a joke.
还真好笑...
Uh, good one.
是啊
Yep.
你已经知道我的名字了
You already know my name.
我大半辈子都住在加州的Tustin
I lived most of my life in Tustin, California.
好的...还有你旅行的原因?
Cool. And reason for travel?
你在澳大利亚的原因?
The reason you were in Australia?
我在找东西
I was looking for something.
找东西 ... 啊哈
Looking. Uh-huh.
好极了
Right on.
找一些东西
Something.
那么你找到了吗?
So, did you find it?
没  它找到我了
No, it found me.
还需要知道些什么吗?
Anything else?
不  没了  很好
No, no, that's good.
谢谢
Uh, thanks.
嘿呃我知道我已经和你谈过了
Hey, uh, I know I already talked to you,
我只是想离开他一会儿
but I just wanted to get away from him for a second.
你看到昨晚有谁离开海岸了?
Did you see anyone leave the beach last night?
人们来来往往  但...
People come and go, but...
不  我不知道
No, I don't know.
什么?
What?
我不知道是否真有其事
I'm not sure anything happened.
什么意思?
Wait, what?
Claire告诉我和Michael 袭击者试图用东西刺她
Claire told Michael and I that this attacker tried to inject her with something.
但她腹部并没有伤痕
But there was no mark on her stomach.
她两次都是在连续的尖叫声中醒来
She wakes up two nights screaming.
第一次她是在梦游
First time, sleepwalking.
你认为这都是她编造出来的?她受到惊吓了伙计
Think she's making this up? She was terrified.
听她说那家伙要伤害她的孩子
She said he was hurting her baby.
大家都睡在周围 那个人为什么要这么做?
Why would someone do that With us 20 feet away?
-所以你认为她是在撒谎?  -不
-You think she's lying?  -No.
-怀孕的女子头脑尤其清醒  -头脑清醒对
-Pregnant woman have extremely lucid...  -Lucid.
这些就是典型的"噩梦焦虑症"
Textbook anxiety nightmares.
你对大家的情况都很了解?
You know everything that's going on with everyone?
那么我们该怎么做?
So, what do we do?
Claire的预产期只有一周多一点了 或许两周
Claire's due in a little more than a week. Maybe two.
但如果她的神经再绷得这么紧 或者再受到一次惊吓
But if she stays stressed out like this
会造成早产的
or has another panic attack,
而这儿没有手术工具 没有监控器  也没麻醉剂
it could trigger an early labor. Out here with no instruments, no monitors, no anesthetic...
事情会很不妙的
That would not be good.
她还没想过这些
It's not all in her head.
-嘿 Lance  -抱歉?
-Hey, Lance.  -Sorry?
Lance你叫Lance对吧?
Lance. Your name's Lance, right?
-Ethan  -老兄  哦对
-Ethan.  -Dude, that's right.
Lance是个瘦瘦的小伙 带着眼镜  红头发
Lance is a skinny guy with glasses and red hair.
我觉得你把我们都搞混了
I can see how you'd confuse us.
对不起  老兄  名字太多了 面孔太多了  我真是累啊
Sorry, dude. Lots of names and faces.
你和岛上的这些人 都已经相处好几周了
Pathetic. You'd think after a couple weeks on the island with the same people,
大家都应该相互了解了
we'd know each other.
是的  你说得没错 你会有这种想法的
You're right. You would think so.
我们在列清单
So we're doing this list,
所有的生还者的姓名 家庭住址之类的东西
all the survivors' names, home addresses, stuff like that.
好  你已经知道我的名字了
Okay, well, you already have my name.
-好的  不叫Lance  -绝对不是
-All right, not Lance.  -Definitely not.
-姓什么?  -Rom
-Last name?  -Rom.
-Rom ... "r-o-m"?  -是的
-Rom, R-O-M?  -That's right.
很好你是哪里人  Ethan Rom?
Great. Where you from, Ethan Rom?
-安大略湖  -好极了  我喜欢加拿大
-Ontario.  -Right on. Love Canada. Great, uh...
好的
Well,
都记下了 感谢你抽出时间  老兄
that should do it. Thanks for your time, dude.
你记这些干什么用?
Hey, what's this for?
没什么...只是我个人觉得这是个好主意
Oh, it's nothing. Just, you know, thought it'd be a good idea.
Claire?
你找到他了?
Did you find him?
呃  没有
Um, no.
要是他再回来怎么办?
What if he comes back?
Claire我们碰到的这种情况
Claire...This situation that we're in,
坠机...没人到这地方来救我们
the crash, that no one's coming, this place,
这都会在你的脑中形成一种混乱
it can kind of mess with your head a little
或许还会让你的感觉失真
and make you see things that aren't actually there.
-我知道那感觉非常真实  -我不明白
-Now, I know it feels very real...  -I don't under...
你要生孩子了 ... 很快
Look, your baby's coming. ... Soon.
我甚至无法想象 这对你来说有多么的恐惧
And I can't even imagine how scary that must be for you.
但是你感觉越不安 你就会越危险
But the more upset you are, the more dangerous it is for you,
还会涉及到你的孩子
and your baby.
所以我要你吃这些药
So I want you to take these.
这是什么?
What are they?
这是镇静药
It's a sedative.
药力比较温和 通常适用于你这样的情况
Very mild, commonly used in situations like yours.
对孩子不会有伤害  我保证
It won't harm the baby. I promise.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
Claire
你认为这是我编造出来的?
You think I'm making this up?
我受到了攻击 你却给我安眠药?
I get attacked, and you want to give me sleeping pills?
这不是安眠药 ... 听着 这是一种非常温和的镇定药物  Claire
They're not sleeping...Look, it's a very mild sedative.
-我要走了  -什么?  不行!  Claire
-I'm leaving.  -What? No! Claire. Claire...
在海边会安全点 这儿并不安全
It was safe at the beach. It’s not safe here.
不要这么做  Claire 你得考虑到你的孩子  Claire
Don't do this. Think about the baby.
不要和我谈孩子的事情
Don't talk to me about the baby.
我讨厌人们告诉我该怎么做
I'm sick of everyone telling me what to do.
-求你了  -让我走
-Please...  -Let go of me.
你没事吧?
You okay?
你对她说什么了?
What did you say to her?
什么事?
Yes?
-Malkin先生我们以前见过吗?  -是的  我记得
-Mr. Malkin, we met before?  -Yes, I remember.
当时你不肯给我算命 希望你现在不要拒绝
You wouldn't give me a reading. I was hoping you would now.
如果你能通灵 为什么还要数钱?
If you're a psychic, why do you have to count it?
算命可不是数钱算出来的
That's not how it works.
我只是开个玩笑
I was just joking.
-那么你是如何算出来的?  -我不知道
-So... how does it work?  -I don't know.
他什么时候离开你的?
When did he leave you?
上周
Last week.
上次你不肯给我算命 是因为这件事吗?
Is that why you didn't want to do my reading?
不  上次我看到了些东西 一些比较模糊的东西
No, no, no. I saw something, sort of a blurry thing.
-模糊中透露出不好?  -不好
-And Blurry's bad?  -Blurry's bad.
那才是我停止给你算命的原因
That's why I stopped the reading.
你确定这次要我继续给你算命?
Are you sure you want to go on now?
是的  麻烦你
Yes, please.
我可以告诉你
I can tell you,
这非常重要
this is important.
好的
Okay.
你必须自己抚养这个孩子 这一点至关重要
It is crucial that you, yourself, raise this child.
你意思是和Thomas一起抚养?他是...
You mean with Thomas? Is he...?
孩子的父亲不能进入孩子的生活领域也不能进入你的
The father of this child will play no part in its life, nor yours.
那么你到底想表达什么意思?
So, what exactly are you saying?
这孩子如果让除你之外的任何人抚养
This child parented by anyone else, anyone other than you...
孩子将会有危险
Danger surrounds this baby.
危险?
Danger?
你的本性  你的精神
Your nature, your spirit,
你的善良一定得影响到孩子的成长
your goodness must be an influence in the development of this child.
听着  如果Thomas和我不能和好的话
Look, if Thomas and I don’t, you know, get back together,
我就会让别人收养我的孩子
I'm putting this baby up for adoption.
我只是想来搞清楚怎样才能给我孩子一个快乐的人生
I just wanted to find out what would give the baby the happiest life.
没有快乐的人生
There is no happy life.
没有你  孩子就不会有这样的快乐
Not for this child, not without you.
-我不...  -不能让其他人收养
-I don't...  -There can't be another.
你不准让其他人收养你的孩子
You mustn't allow another to raise your baby.
好  棒极了
Okay. Great.
-感谢你拿了我的200美元  -听着  钱你拿着
-Thanks for taking my 200.  -Look, take it.
Littleton小姐 我求你考虑一下
Miss Littleton,I am begging you just to consider...
我不能自己抚养这个孩子
I can't raise this child by myself.
你必须听我的!
You have to listen to me!
好感谢你抽出时间 还把钱还给了我!
Thanks for your time and my money back!
Littleton女士求你了!孩子需要你的保护!
The baby needs your protection!
Littleton女士!
Miss Littleton!
求你了!
Please!
喂?
Hello?
Littleton女士  我是Richard Malkin
Miss Littleton, it's Richard Malkin.
上帝
Oh, my God.
听我说我有个计划 一个会让事情好转的计划
Listen to me. I have a plan, something that will make this all better.
你不要再打电话给我了
You've got to stop calling me.
太晚了  好吗?我明天就去收养中心了
It's too late, all right? I’m going to see Adoptive Services tomorrow.
我已经告诉你几个月了 你不能这么做
I've been telling you for months, you cannot do that.
我怎么处理我的孩子 不关你的事
What I do with my baby is none of your business.
如果你不按照我跟你说的做
If you don't do what I'm suggesting,
将有大祸降临于你和你的孩子
great danger will befall...
不  如果你半夜三更 还这样给我打电话的话
Great danger will befall you if you don't stop calling me
你才会倒大霉
In the middle of the night.
我知道你内心什么感受  Claire
I know what you're feeling inside.
你在考虑你是否真要把孩子送人
You're doubting your decision to give up the baby.
听着  算我求你  不要这么做 至少先听听我的计划
Look, I'm begging you, don't do it. At least hear my plan first.
晚安
Good night.
你去哪?
Where are you going?
回海边去
Back to the beach.
发生什么事了?
Well, what happened?
-Jack他...  -Jack想给我灌药
-Did Jack...?  -Jack tried to dope me.
他认为这些都是我编造出来的
He thinks I'm making all this up,
这些事其实并没有发生
that none of it really happened.
对所以为了证明你清醒的很 你就想一个人穿过这片丛林
Right. So, to prove your sanity, you go tromping through the jungle alone.
做得好
Well done.
我没有疯  Charlie
I'm not crazy, Charlie.
你要我的信息?
You want my information?
名字  Shannon Rutherford
Name: Shannon Rutherford.
年龄  20
Age: 20.
住址  Craphole岛
Address: Craphole Island.
那么昨晚你俩去哪了?
So, uh, where were you guys last night?
海边
Um, the beach.
你调查干什么?
Why the interrogation?
你是第20个问我这个问题的人
You're like the twentieth person to ask me that.
为什么人们对回答一些问题感到紧张?
Why is everyone uptight about answering questions?
也许人们对你设立"爱国者法案"不太满意
Well, maybe we're just not cool with you setting up your own little Patriot Act, man.
他是个自由主义者
He's a liberal.
说真的为什么要列清单?
Seriously, why the list?
没什么  只是昨晚山谷里面发生了点意外
It's nothing. We had an incident in the valley last night.
意外?
An incident?
是的Claire那个怀孕的女孩 你认识她吗?
Yeah, Claire, the pregnant girl. You know her?
她...可以说是受到了攻击
She, uh, kind of got attacked.
-什么?!   -她没事吧?
-What?  -She okay?
是的...她有点惊吓过度但...
Yeah, she's a little shook up, but...
我才不搬去那个鬼山洞!
I am not moving to the Rape Caves.
你知道去找张旅客名单事情就好办多了
Your life would be much easier if you just had the manifest.
我们烧机身的时候已经把死者的名字划去了
We crossed out names of the dead after we burned the fuselage,
所以我们生还者的名字都登记在册的
so should be a full roster of the rest of us.
什么?真的吗?谁有?
What? Really? Who has it?
你觉得呢?
Who do you think?
我就开门见山了
I'm just gonna lay it out straight.
好的  你说吧
Okay, you do that.
我听说你有旅客名单
I hear you have the flight manifest,
我要用 所以我要你把它给我
and I need it and want you to give it to me.
就这样?
That so?
现在你可以做出反应了 人们请你帮忙时  你都会这么做的
Now, you could do what you normally do when someone asks for something,
告诉我"滚开"
tell me to screw off.
滚开?
Screw off?
或者你可以把它给我
Or you could just give it to me.
因为老兄你品德很好
'Cause, dude, you could use the points.
老天  你可真会奉承  胖子
Well, gosh, you sure know how to butter a man up, Stay-Puff.
这是天赋
It's a gift.
旅客名单在褐色的手提箱里 你拿去吧
Manifest is in the brown suitcase. Take it.
我来帮你背包吧
Please let me carry your bag.
我能行
I'm fine.
我知道你能行 但还是我来背包吧
I know you're fine, but I can carry your bag.
为什么你老跟在我后面?
Why did you come after me?
可能是因为我喜欢你吧
Well, it's probably because I like you.
什么?
What?
你不喜欢我  Charlie 你明白吗?
You don't like me, Charlie, okay?
你想救我只是因为我...
You just want to rescue me because I'm...
因为这东西
Because of this.
但我没事好吧?我不需要援救  我不...
But I'm fine, okay? I don't need rescuing. I don't need...
Claire?
什么? 怎么了? Claire? 你怎么了?
What? Claire, what? What is it?
-又宫缩了?  -是的
-Was that another one?  -Yeah.
好的...我们得计算宫缩频率
We need to time the contractions.
那就是你要做的 计算宫缩频率  好吗?
That's what you do. Time the contractions, okay?
一个糖李子仙女 两个糖李子仙女
One sugar plum fairy, two sugar plum fairy...
你得平静下来好吗?
You just need to calm down, all right?
深呼吸
Big deep breaths.
Charlie我要你去把Jack叫来
I need you to go get Jack.
-什么?  -我没事的
-What?  -I'll be all right.
我不会留下你一个人的 我会接生小孩
I'm not leaving you alone. I can deliver a baby.
-我能做到的  -拜托去叫吧!
-I can do this.  -Please, go!
Charlie你不知道如何接生
You don't know how to...
等等...听我说 我不会再让你发生意外的
Listen.I might not know what I'm doing,
我或许不知道怎么做 但我会想出来的
but I'll figure it out.
我既然能戒毒 我就能接生孩子
If I can kick drugs,I can deliver a baby.
让我解释 我沉迷于毒品
Let me explain. I'm a drug addict.
我曾经沉迷于毒品 我现在已经戒掉了
I was a drug addict. I'm clean now.
叫Jack去!
Get Jack!
好的
Right.
Arlene和Joseph将带你去墨尔本
Arlene and Joseph will bring you to Melbourne.
他们会付给你生活与医疗费用
They'll pay your living and medical expenses.
我们给你找了间公寓 有两个卧室真的很好而且
We found you an apartment. It’s a really nice two-bedroom place,
而且我们认为你会住得很舒适的
and we think you're gonna be really comfortable in it.
正如我们先前说好的 孩子一出生就要交给Stewarts夫妇
As discussed, once the baby's born and handed over to the Stewarts,
你以后再也没权力去看望这个孩子
you'll have no right to see the child again.
你也没权力和孩子联络
You'll have no right to correspond with the child,
至于是否告诉孩子关于你的事
it will be entirely up to Arlene and Joseph
一切都得由Arlene和Joseph决定
to decide whether to tell the child anything about you.
明白吗?
Understood?
是的
Yes.
除了医院的费用
Upon your discharge from the hospital,
他们将额外再支付你20000美元
you will be given an additional payment of $20,000.
我只是想确保你们会真的照顾好孩子
I just want to make sure that you're gonna take really good care of the baby.
我们当然会的
Of course we will.
现在我需要你在协议下面签字写上日期
Now, I'll need you to sign and date here where indicated.
你知道"Catch a falling star"这首歌吗?
Do you know Catch a Falling Star?
这首歌像摇篮曲
It's a song, like a lullaby.
"Catch a falling star and put it in your pocket"
小时候我爸就常唱给我听
My dad used to sing that to me when I was little.
你们能有空给孩子唱这首歌吗?
Do you think you could sing it to the baby once in a while?
当然
Of course.
-这支笔没墨水了  -用这支
-It's not working.  -Here.
我 ... 我 ... 我很抱歉 我不能这么做
I'm...I'm... I'm sorry. I can't do this.
什么?不!不!
What? No! No!
是什么?  你的建议是什么?
Okay, what is it? What’s your offer?
感谢上帝! 你叫什么名字来着?
Thank God! What's your name?
Ethan你行吗?
Ethan. Are you all right?
你得跑去山洞那儿叫Jack
Go the caves. Run to the caves. Get Jack.
-告诉他Claire...  -Claire她没事吧?
-Tell him Claire...  -Claire. She okay?
她要生了快去好吗?
She's having the baby. Go fast, okay?
我和她在一起 ... 就在那边的小路
I'll be with her, on the path there.
快去!
Go!
Claire!
我在这儿!
I'm here!
Claire!好的  Jack马上就来
Claire! Okay, Jack's coming.
感觉怎么样?
How you doing?
很疼
It hurts.
好  抓住我的手
Okay, just take my hand.
紧握
Squeeze.
好的 呼吸
Okay, breathe.
吸气  呼气
Inhale. Exhale.
很好  呼吸
Good. Just breathe.
吸气 好...很好
Inhale. Okay, good.
我本不应该来这儿的
Oh, I'm not supposed to be here.
我俩都有这个想法
We all feel like that a little bit.
我知道只是
I know. It's just...
有人向我保证事情不会这样的
Someone promised me it would be different.
但他说错了
Well, he was wrong.
是的他说错了
Yeah. He was wrong.
你用四个月的时间告诉我 我得自己抚养这个孩子
You spent the last four months telling me I have to raise the baby myself.
现在你却给我钱 说我不必这么做?
Now you're giving me money and saying I don't have to?
我在洛杉矶找到了一对 渴望收养孩子的夫妇
I found a couple in Los Angeles who are very eager to adopt.
孩子在他们的照管下会很安全的
The baby will be safe in their care.
-现在我预见到  -你预见到?!
-Now, I've foreseen...  -You've foreseen.
我甚至不知道我为什么来这儿 抱歉
I don't even know why I'm here. I'm sorry.
我知道这听起来很荒唐 Claire  所有这些占星学的东西
I know this sounds ridiculous, Claire, all this psychic business,
我知道你一定会认为 我是个胡言乱语的疯子
and I appreciate that you must think I'm a raving madman.
但该来的总会来的
But this is what must happen.
那么你会给我6000美元
So you're giving me $6,000
把我的孩子送给洛杉矶的一对陌生夫妇?
to give my baby to a couple of strangers in Los Angeles?
12000美元
$12,000.
另外6000美元等你到洛杉矶的时候再给你
The other six when you arrive in Los Angeles.
他们不是陌生人Claire 他们是一对好夫妇
And they're not strangers, Claire. They’re good people.
-那种古里古怪的人?  -我知道这很另人难为情
-A psychic?  -I know. It's embarrassing.
经历了这么多 他真的很关心这件事
And after everything, he was just full of it.
或许不关心
Or not.
我意思是他的想法是 不要让任何人领养你的孩子对吧?
I mean, all he wanted was that no one else raise your baby, right?
或许他早就知道了
Maybe he knew.
我是说
I mean,
如果他想让事情变得足够的糟糕
if you wanted it bad enough...
你知道...如果他有那种天赋
You know, if he had the gift,
我相信有些人有...
and I believe some people do...
那么他早就知道 会发生这样的事  Claire
Maybe he knew, Claire.
明天我不能去 我得去取我的...
I can't go tomorrow. I have to get my...
必须得坐这个航班 不能选其它的
It has to be this flight. It can't be any other.
你抵达的时候 他们已经安排好和你会面了
They're already scheduled to meet you when you arrive.
815号航班 815号航班
Flight 815. Flight 815.
洛杉矶根本没那对夫妇
There was no couple in Los Angeles.
他早知道了
He knew.
他知道飞机会...
He knew about the plane,
会发生什么事...
what was gonna happen...
上帝...他居然知道
Oh, my God, he knew.
感觉又要宫缩了吗?
You feel another one coming?
我不觉得
I don't think so.
Jack到底去哪了?
Where the hell is Jack?
我想...
You know, I think...
我想我没事了
I think I'm all right.
宫缩吗?
The contractions?
或许那是最后一次宫缩
Maybe that was the last one.
希望那就是最后一次吧
Please, let that have been the last one.
Jack说过压力会导致分娩的假象
Jack said that stress can cause a false labor.
你确定没事?
You sure you're all right?
不疼了
No pain.
避开紧急分娩了
Birthing emergency averted.
我说过我会照顾好你的
I told you I'd take care of you.
谢谢你Charlie
Thanks, Charlie.
你太客气了
You're quite welcome.
你觉得你能坚持回到山洞吗?
You think you can make it back to the caves?
我不会让你发生任何意外
I won't let anything happen to you.
好的
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
Sayid
听我说
Listen to me.
我找到她了 ... 那个法国女子
I found her, the Frenchwoman.
我需要水
I need some water.
那个岛上的女子
The woman on the island...
我得赶回来 我得赶回来
I had to come back. I had to come back.
岛上并不止我们这些人
We're not alone.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是是的他刚刚踢了我一下
Yeah, yeah, he just kicked.
这儿
Here.
我发现个问题
We got a problem.
这旅客名单
The manifest.
Jack...人口调查
Jack, the census,
存活者的名单
the names of everyone who survived.
总共是46个人
All 46 of us.
我和每个人碰过面了 包括这里的和海边的
I interviewed everyone, here, at the beach.
我都拿到了他们的名字
I got their names.
其中一个... 其中有一个...
One of them...One of them isn't...
Jack
其中一个并不在旅客名单上
One of them isn't in the manifest.
他没坐飞机
He wasn't on the plane.
两位好啊
Hello, there.
Ethan...Jack在哪?
Ethan, where's Jack?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====